<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teaching on The Everyday Quantum Mechanic</title>
    <link>https://bdsmith147.github.io/everydayquantummechanic/teaching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teaching on The Everyday Quantum Mechanic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 21:40:25 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdsmith147.github.io/everydayquantummechanic/teaching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy</title>
      <link>https://bdsmith147.github.io/everydayquantummechanic/teaching/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 16:45:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdsmith147.github.io/everydayquantummechanic/teaching/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Statement of Teaching Philosophy Introduction: The Necessity of Belief In conversation, when people learn I’m a physicist they often reply along the lines of, “Oh, I’m not smart enough to do that.” This reply reveals the common belief in the “fixed mindset”: that someone’s success and ability to learn is a product of their innate talents, and that these aptitudes cannot be changed1. In contrast, I learned from my mother at a young age the simple phrase, “If you believe you can, or if you believe you can’t, you’re right”2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Development</title>
      <link>https://bdsmith147.github.io/everydayquantummechanic/teaching/professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 16:45:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdsmith147.github.io/everydayquantummechanic/teaching/professional/</guid>
      <description>GTLP As a PhD student at the University of Alberta, I participated in the Graduate Teaching and Learning Program (GTLP). This program is designed to help graduate students learn and engage with best practices and the scholarship of teaching, learning, and course design. It supports graduate students in their development as educators and future primary instructors.
🔸 I have completed Levels 1, 2, and 3 of GTLP.
 The following are several artifacts from my participation in GTLP Level 3, produced between January to April 2022:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student Feedback</title>
      <link>https://bdsmith147.github.io/everydayquantummechanic/teaching/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 16:45:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdsmith147.github.io/everydayquantummechanic/teaching/feedback/</guid>
      <description>These are selected, anonymous student feedback comments I&amp;rsquo;ve received about my teaching:
 &amp;ldquo;He was always willing to help out when I needed. He provided just the right amount of guidence, in that it was the perfect balance of developing my skills individually while also being nudged in the right direction when I asked a question. Ben was very exceptional, one of the best TAs I&amp;rsquo;ve ever had. He was also available to meet outside of lab hours so that I could ask him a question, and he gave me some great feedback to improve my writing skills in a research context as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Experience</title>
      <link>https://bdsmith147.github.io/everydayquantummechanic/teaching/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 16:45:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdsmith147.github.io/everydayquantummechanic/teaching/experience/</guid>
      <description>I have been involved in various teaching roles since early in my academic career.
Adjunct Principle Instructor Between January to July 2016, I worked as an adjunct principle-instructor at Brigham Young University-Idaho in Rexburg, Idaho, USA. I was responsible for designing and implementing the course layouts, instruction, and assessments for several classes of 20-30 students each:
  PHYS 121, Principles of Physics 1: The first course in the calculus-based sequence of introductory physics for science majors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Main</title>
      <link>https://bdsmith147.github.io/everydayquantummechanic/teaching/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 16:21:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdsmith147.github.io/everydayquantummechanic/teaching/main/</guid>
      <description>Teaching Mission Statement: Inspire learners to expand their potential with me. Encourage an attitude and climate of vulnerability, community, and growth. Model a discipline of intentional practice.
  Statement of Teaching Philosophy  In conversation, when people learn I’m a physicist they often reply along the lines of, “Oh, I’m not smart enough to do that.” This reply reveals the common belief in the “fixed mindset”: that someone’s success and ability to learn is a product of their innate talents,&amp;hellip;Continue reading.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
